gurgaonsaath.com 2015-06-10

# Gurgaonsaath - Privacy Policy

Gurgaonsaath.com is owned and operated by Quail Technology Pvt. Ltd., India. All contents of the website including text, graphics, images, design, logos, and software are products of Quail Technology Pvt. Ltd., India and are protected by copyright and trademark laws. Contents of this site are for information only and are provided to you solely for personal and non-commercial use.

This website and its content may not be copied, uploaded, downloaded, modified, transmitted, licensed, transferred, sold, creative derivatives made or published or otherwise distributed except as expressly permitted. 

**Liability for third party content**

Gurgaonsaathcannot guarantee the accuracy, completeness, integrity and actuality of the content posted by buyers and sellers. In cases of declaration of violation of rights, Gurgaonsaath will delete the concerned content as soon as possible.

**Liability for links**

Gurgaonsaath contains links to external websites over which we have no control. Thus, we cannot be held accountable for the content of those third party websites and the consequences that may arise from the existence of such links.The operator or provider of such content/links is the one responsible for their respective site content. 

A constant and permanent monitoring of the links posted on Gurgaonsaath is deemed unreasonable and infeasible. But in cases of declaration of violation of rights, Gurgaonsaath will delete the concerned link(s) as soon as possible.

**Collection and processing of personal data**

Ads posted on Gurgaonsaath are obviously made available to the public. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you are consenting to the transfer and storage of that information to and on our servers.

**We collect and store the following personal information**

Email address, physical location and contact information (depending on the service used)

Computer sign-in data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Gurgaonsaath as well as ad data (Through cookies which you can disable on your browser. However, this is likely to affect your ability to use the site in terms of functionality).

Other information including your IP address and standard web log information.

**Transfer of personal data**

Transfer or provision of personal data to a third party occurs only if Gurgaonsaath is lawfully obligated to provide information to authorities in relation to an ad that a user has posted, or if the user has given prior consent to the release of personal data. Otherwise, personal data will not be released, shared or sold to third parties for marketing or advertising purposes without prior permission from the user.

**Cookies**

Gurgaonsaath uses cookies in connection with the web browser for optimum usage of the site. We use cookies to remember the last activity of the user on the website, for the user's own convenience. This applies in terms of saving the user's details (username and password) and settings on applications. Cookies are used to identify the used computer. No personal data except the user’s IP address is saved.

The user may choose to disable or adjust enabled cookies accordingly by configuring their web browser. However, disabling or deleting cookies may result in the unavailability of some functions and features of the website.

**Data protection policies**

Our data protection policies only apply to Gurgaonsaath and do not cover external websites/links/content or the external activities of the users and the consequences arising thereafter. We offer users a platform to interact with other users (buyers and sellers) and post ads.

**Right of withdrawal of information/links**

Personal information provided to Gurgaonsaath may be requested for deletion at any time. If you have given the permission for the transmission of personal information to a third party, you may at any time cancel or withdraw this permission.

Contact us regarding any more questions and concernson data privacy and protection.
